Jhal
Hello
friends in today's video we will talk about
those factors in those possibilities, on the
basis of Deep, tomorrow we are going to do our 10 hour,
so if you are on this channel and you should
not update this video like this
because in this video we have some
important points of tomorrow, so let's start,
as in yesterday's video
we discussed that if this friend
sustains above 5100 then you can
see a special labor in Nifty
and today we have to see such a stitch,
but after breaking the he gives a cloth, there is
a short covering in it and this
finally we are given a team 125 club spectro
and if we talk about the
global of the index, then here again the
script today almost has to be selected
and suicide in tax planning soil and
in that soil we have to
see the
color of the channel from here, again this is a medium that
with your of birth you will get to see a consolidation from sweet
because
except for some stars of the bank, the rest of the Happy Birthday,
in this you will see a little long  Many
can be selected to solve problems quickly. You
can't use your tempered glass on the gym.
So first of all, let's talk about clay juice. This is a
continuous shift.
This channel can be viewed once. After a single note
formation, we can see that
if a Hussain is 200 feet or less,
you will see a slight condition bar.
And if you are setting up futures and options, let me
tell you that the market here may
also connect a little after tomorrow
because there are still fluctuations in the global market. It is almost
like consolidation here. I am seeing this.
Provided, do something once before buying the next cigarette tomorrow.
Or if this is
not the same as searching on 232, then you will find any
[music]
option. And if there is a recipe here, then
it means only one thing. If we
go to media short covering from here, we may see a small good thing,
but the
spelling scenario is still
intact. So, unless a pin
contact is deleted here, then we  Any address will
not just go to Indramani and call contract
and if it subscribes above 10
then you can add another contact of 100 beds here on the
scalp read side
and after that you click on friends so
because of this here today
including ICICI Bank and for this reason today
and
if this
20 is above this then looking at the next coming
thanks record here, two here
Dharmendra and we will do a laundry in this tomorrow on fuel consumption
that
Kepler you also have to take a tilak of this thing
that if this leave above 120 for 5 minutes and one
minute can you understand then you can
create a position for long time in quality that let me
tell those who take tweets in options, here at
4522 surprising here today
contractor is Edward, looking at which
you have in current scenario here
that Shot Ganesh appointment question is Dainik
Prabhat Karo Benefit here below tomorrow
call at office  The unwinding is going on and
we're still adding contacts to that above. So
guys, without doing this forty verses,
you can
interpret the charge sound contact from here for 150
because Annie is now on the side and that
too because of ICICI Bank and these
are on the sides. So you'll easily
see 41518 only in between. So guys,
now let's talk about the staff that we're going to
print tomorrow. How are you doing right now?
[Music]
I just say the first store is the same
Ixnc hair oil ad here. In the last
few days, at least five days, we've been able to make a significant
difference. One such stitching, we have
a big low in the first channel of the day at a horse square
and then we continue celebrating.
We have a
declared marriage here today. So guys,
now the
point is below the skirt here. You can
see Aniket behind Sector 20 in the profit sales office.
And when the second account comes, you can
take a straight line.  We will cut it now it is on the scalp, you
can take one after login cotton
and you have water percentile in that case you should
face your real estate
gas crime should train other staff let me
tell you this rate is here
after stock split and after permission of q2 results
we get to see a proper soldier in the stock here the stock which
was more interested in the market was
due to the growth of plate hair here to a large extent it
can only continue for some time
opinion if we start below zero then
you will
see ₹50 per dancer in the market here next9news you
can connect your profit booking here on this topic 2017 52062 but if you liked the video then
please like and share and if you want then you can
also connect the icon along with subscribing so that
you can get such updates
sometimes Bigg Boss
progress then the third stock locks
you can try this treatment IIT cashew abs has been
quite volatile and today  Zensar
Technologies, which was once a midcap cycle
stock limit explanation-current what tax
stock IT stocks and so here also today
we are told to see a use nine person start here
that guide here we have seen this thing
and it prevents the near result
from being declared, so this thing can be
used as a tube on your side,
if from here if we see any comments that we
want to leave, then
you will definitely see an alarm set of ₹10 in that topic very easily
and in that case
escape and we will cook in our profit,
so our next target will be tomorrow
2036 and for developers on this we have
looted that if you should continue straight ahead then
you should register your stop
asking questions which we are going to do here around dowry, those who should
treat their last staff,
stock comes infrastructure and this
statement should stock India first year
state and today after one slot water from Promise Feet,
if you look at the development that has come in this index, in this
we have India Bulls Real
Accused sent in estate today is eyeing
so let's today in around 600 an alarm
set a hang report comes and right now the
stock will give suitable trips below current lunch
so tomorrow you will get 13050 and 108 trailers
such tight container dress that's all in this video
if you liked the video then
please like and share and if you have
not subscribed to our channel yet then you will find it
in the description below there you will find
farmer information folded before the market opens
and if you
want our skins present there the
position of train tracks
updates madam then you can join our group AIB
number shipyard kids you can
see it below so see you
in the next video till then thank you so much and half in you
in next month
[music]